Today's news is an absolute bombshell
la noticia de hoy es una absoluta bomba
Tele5 Mediaset radically breaks with the
tele5 mediaset rompe radicalmente con la
TV factory the
fábrica de la tele se acabaron los
work on the TV factory at
trabajos de la fábrica de la tele en
Mediaset has ended Definitely everything that was the
mediaset Definitivamente todo lo que era
TV factory of Tele5 was leaving
fábrica de la tele de tele5 se iba yendo
Socialite is there, everything is a lie
socialité está el todo es mentira
also okay obviously What must
también vale evidentemente Ahí lo que
have happened and what must have been affected is
habrá pasado y lo que habrá afectado es
that 30% that belongs to Mediaset of the
ese 30% que pertenece a media s de la
TV factory So now things
fábrica de la tele Entonces ya la cosa
are unsustainable things have gone
es insostenible la cosa ya ha ido a
completely downhill and they want
pique totalmente y nos quieren
absolutely nothing from the
absolutamente nada de la fábrica de la
TV factory one of the causes of
tele se señala como una de las causas de
this resounding loss of audience is pointed out as the
esta contundente pérdida de audiencia el
use and abuse of a position so marked
uso y abuso de una posición tan marcada
in favor of one of the parties Okay when
a favor de una de las partes Vale cuando
we say one of the parties we are
decimos una de las partes se están
referring to the parties Antonio Avid
refiriendo a las partes Antonio avid
Rosito
rosito